Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series A: Miscellaneous, August 1937-May 1938
  - Photo Unit #: A200 [view of the city with damage], Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1247)
  - Photo Unit #: A203 Bridge, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1248)
  - Photo Unit #: A204 Damaged building, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0873)
  - Photo Unit #: A212 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Machine-Gunner Company headquarters [in cave]; Makela, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1249)
  - Photo Unit #: A214 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Teruel [3 men with cooking pot], 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1250)
  - Photo Unit #: A215 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0874)
  - Photo Unit #: A217 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1251)
  - Photo Unit #: A218 Pablo Carbonell, killed in action, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0875)
  - Photo Unit #: A220 Bombardment, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1252)
  - Photo Unit #: A222 Small farm building, explosions in the distance (Box 6, Folder 11-1857)
  - Photo Unit #: A224 Estado Mayor "central" [Headquarters], Transmiciones [Transmissions], Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0876)
  - Photo Unit #: A225 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0877)
  - Photo Unit #: A228 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0878)
  - Photo Unit #: A230 MacKenzie-Papineau, [3 men in] trench, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1253)
    Available Formats: Print
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/28)
  - Photo Unit #: A241 MacKenzie-Papineau, [2 men in] trenches, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 5, Folder 11-1254)
  - Photo Unit #: A242 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Seguro de Los Baños [torn and damaged print], 1938-02 (Box 5, Folder 11-1255)
  - Photo Unit #: A243 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 5, Folder 11-1256)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Print; Moscow negative
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/11)
  - Photo Unit #: A245 First aid in MacKenzie-Papineau trench, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 5, Folder 11-1257)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/10)
  - Photo Unit #: A246 Mackenzie-Papineau [soldier] in trench with sighting device (Box 3, Folder 11-1858)
  - Photo Unit #: A249 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0589)
  - Photo Unit #: A250 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0590)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/18)
  - Photo Unit #: A251 Two Mackenzie-Papineau soldiers in trench (Box 6, Folder 11-1859)
  - Photo Unit #: A254 Mackenzie-Papineau soldiers in trench fortification (Box 6, Folder 11-1860)
  - Photo Unit #: A255 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, 1938-02 (Box 5, Folder 11-1258)
  - Photo Unit #: A256 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0591)
  - Photo Unit #: A258 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, [working on a machine gun], 1938-02 (Box 6, Folder 11-1763)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/54)
  - Photo Unit #: A259 MacKenzie-Papineau position, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 6, Folder 11-1829)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/5)
  - Photo Unit #: A262 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion after Seguro de Los Baños, [two soldiers with a machine gun], 1938-02 (Box 6, Folder 11-1837)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/26)
  - Photo Unit #: A267 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0592)
  - Photo Unit #: A268 MacKenzie-Papineau soldier in trench firing rifle (Box 6, Folder 11-1861)
  - Photo Unit #: A269 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños [2 men in trench], 1938-02 (Box 5, Folder 11-1259)
  - Photo Unit #: A270 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0593)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/37)
  - Photo Unit #: A271 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0594)
  - Photo Unit #: A274 View from MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Seguro de Los Baños, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0595)
  - Photo Unit #: A279 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0879)
  - Photo Unit #: A280 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1260)
  - Photo Unit #: A281 American Artillery unit emplacement, Teruel front, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0880)
  - Photo Unit #: A283 American Artillery unit emplacement, Teruel front, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0881)
  - Photo Unit #: A284 American Artillery unit emplacement, Teruel front, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0882)
  - Photo Unit #: A286 American Artillery unit emplacement, Teruel front [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1938-01 (Box 6, Folder 11-1884)
  - Photo Unit #: A289 British Battalion on maneuvers, Mondejar, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0883)
  - Photo Unit #: A290 Fascist posters on the square, Belchite, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0596)
  - Photo Unit #: A291 Street scene, Belchite, 1937-08 (Box 2, Folder 11-0597)
  - Photo Unit #: A292 Street scene, Belchite, 1937-08 (Box 2, Folder 11-0598)
  - Photo Unit #: A294 MacKenzie-Papineau group poses for the camera (Box 6, Folder 11-1862)
  - Photo Unit #: A295 MacKenzie-Papineau Transmiciones [Transmissions]: William (Red) Brown and [?], Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0884)
  - Photo Unit #: A296 Lincoln-Washington front lines, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0885)
  - Photo Unit #: A300 British Battalion Machine-Gunner nest, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0886)
  - Photo Unit #: A301 British Battalion, Company crew machine-gun nest, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1261)
  - Photo Unit #: A306 Transmiciones [Transmissions] repairing Estado Mayor [Headquarters] telephone, Valeverde, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-0887)
  - Photo Unit #: A313 Group at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0888)
  - Photo Unit #: A316 Engineers working on dugouts (Hiyar), 1938-03 (Box 6, Folder 11-1764)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/66)
  - Photo Unit #: A317 Observers, Aragon Retreat, Marcelina Marot and Harvey Hall, Lebux, 1938-03 (Box 5, Folder 11-1262)
  - Photo Unit #: A318 Engineers building refugios, Lebux, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-0889)
  - Photo Unit #: A320 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches [?], Seguro de Los Baños [view over fields to factories in distance], undated (Box 5, Folder 11-1263)
  - Photo Unit #: A321 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 5, Folder 11-1264)
  - Photo Unit #: A323 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Ebro Front, undated (Box 5, Folder 11-1265)
  - Photo Unit #: A324 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Ebro Front, 1938-05 (Box 2, Folder 11-0599)
  - Photo Unit #: A326 15th International Brigade troops marching, Mollerusa, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0890)
  - Photo Unit #: A328 Dr. Mark Straus, 1938-05 (Box 1, Folder 11-0115)
  - Photo Unit #: A330 Panorama, Codo [with church and houses], 1937-08 (Box 5, Folder 11-1266)
  - Photo Unit #: A332 Our artillery firing at Belchite, 1937-09 (Box 5, Folder 11-1267)
  - Photo Unit #: A335 Five soldiers loading artillery, Belchite[?] (Box 6, Folder 11-1863)
  - Photo Unit #: A337 During the battle, Belchite, 1937-09 (Box 5, Folder 11-1268)
  - Photo Unit #: A338 During the battle, Belchite, 1937-09 (Box 5, Folder 11-1269)
  - Photo Unit #: A339 Church during the battle, Belchite [with carts in foreground], 1937-09 (Box 5, Folder 11-1270)
  - Photo Unit #: A340 Church in Belchite [ruined interior], 1937-09 (Box 5, Folder 11-1271)
  - Photo Unit #: A342 Machine-Gunner crew, British Battalion, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 5, Folder 11-1272)
  - Photo Unit #: A343 Machine-Gunner crew, British Battalion, Tarraga [in tall grass], 1938-05 (Box 5, Folder 11-1273)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/34)
  - Photo Unit #: A344 MacKenzie-Papineau Transmiciones [Transmissions], Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0891)
  - Photo Unit #: A346 Troops of 15th International Brigade on march, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0892)
  - Photo Unit #: A348 15th International Brigade troops on march, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 5, Folder 11-1274)
  - Photo Unit #: A350 Aviation, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0893)
  - Photo Unit #: A352 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Transmiciones [Signal Corps], heliographer, undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1845)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/44)
  - Photo Unit #: A353 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Heliographer, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0894)
  - Photo Unit #: A354 Transmissions, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0895)
  - Photo Unit #: A355 Armorer at work (Harry Farris), Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0896)
  - Photo Unit #: A356 Machine-Gunners on trip from Albacete to Barcelona, Tarraga, 1938-04 (Box 2, Folder 11-0600)
  - Photo Unit #: A357 Two soldiers with machine gun (Box 6, Folder 11-1864)
- Series B: Individual Portraits, September 1937-September 1938
  Series IIB: Individual Portraits, September 1937 - September 1938. The Unit photographers had hoped to photograph every member the 15th Brigade. Although this formidable task was never realized, the 415 portraits in this series depict prominent members of the Brigade including Political Commissars Joseph Dallet, John Robinson, Saul Wellman, George Watt, Archie Brown, and Chief of the Brigade Commissariat Sandor Voros. Portraits of other Brigade members include Chief of Brigade Staff Robert Merriman, Commander Milton Wolff, Commander 15th Brigade Vladimir Copic, Dr. Mark Straus, Volunteer for Liberty editor John Tisa, and writers Alvah Bessie and Edwin Rolfe. This series also includes portraits of Photo Unit photographers Ben Katine and Harry Randall.
  - Photo Unit #: B001 Carl Bradley, former commander of American Company, 24th Battalion, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0601)
  - Photo Unit #: B002 Wally Sabatini, Political Commissar, Company 3, MacKenzie-Papineau, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0602)
  - Photo Unit #: B003 Carl Bradley, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0603)
  - Photo Unit #: B004 John Robinson, Adjutant Political Commissar, 15th International Brigade, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0604)
  - Photo Unit #: B005 Wilton Chite, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, from Musicians Union #802, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0605)
  - Photo Unit #: B006 William Newton Miller, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0606)
  - Photo Unit #: B007 Owen Appleton, Battalion Secretary, Lincoln-Washington, killed at Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-10 (Box 2, Folder 11-0607)
  - Photo Unit #: B008 Philip Detro, Battalion Commander, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-11 (Box 1, Folder 11-0116)
  - Photo Unit #: B009 Vete Zablackas, Transmiciones [Transmissions], 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0608)
  - Photo Unit #: B010 Corporal Louis Zivin, Lincoln-Washington Sanidad [Health], 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0609)
  - Photo Unit #: B011 Dimitri Semenoff, Lincoln-Washington (Yugoslav), 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0610)
  - Photo Unit #: B012 Sergeant [?] Mowbray, Lincoln-Washington Sanidad [Health], 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0611)
  - Photo Unit #: B013 Elkan Wendkos, Machine-Gunner Company, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0612)
  - Photo Unit #: B014 Moe [?] Fishman, Transmiciones [Transmissions], 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0613)
  - Photo Unit #: B016 Radomir Smrcka, Chief of Information, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0614)
  - Photo Unit #: B017 James Bourne, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0615)
  - Photo Unit #: B018 [?] Aguila, 24th Battalion Commander, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0616)
  - Photo Unit #: B021 Thomas MacNulty, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0617)
  - Photo Unit #: B022 Peter Nielson, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0618)
  - Photo Unit #: B023 Kenneth Brown, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0619)
  - Photo Unit #: B024 Dimitri Semenoff, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0620)
  - Photo Unit #: B025 Dimitri Semenoff, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0621)
  - Photo Unit #: B026 Lionel Levick, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, 1937-09 (Box 5, Folder 11-1275)
  - Photo Unit #: B027 John Petrullo, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0622)
  - Photo Unit #: B029 Leon [Leo?] Markowitz, 15th International Brigade Commissariat, 1937-12 (Box 5, Folder 11-1276)
  - Photo Unit #: B030 Ely Sack, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0897)
  - Photo Unit #: B034 Paddy O'Dair, British Battalion, 1937-11 (Box 5, Folder 11-1277)
  - Photo Unit #: B036 Donald Thayer, Lincoln-Washington Battalion Staff, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0623)
  - Photo Unit #: B037 Owen Appleton, Lincoln-Washington Battalion Secretary, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0624)
  - Photo Unit #: B038 Douglas Hitchcock, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Secretary, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0625)
  - Photo Unit #: B039 Jack Kramer, Transmiciones [Transmissions] driver, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0626)
  - Photo Unit #: B040 Ivan Rujevcic, Military Intelligence Service, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0627)
    (Moscow Number: 5/188/12)
  - Photo Unit #: B044 Joseph Sands, food truck, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-10 (Box 2, Folder 11-0628)
  - Photo Unit #: B045 Joseph Dallet, Political Commissar, MacKenzie-Papineau, 1937-10 (Box 2, Folder 11-0629)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/7)
  - Photo Unit #: B046 Alfred Chakin, MacKenzie-Papineau quartermaster, 1937-10 (Box 2, Folder 11-0630)
  - Photo Unit #: B047 Milton Wolff, Adjuntant of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0631)
  - Photo Unit #: B048 George Kay, Lincoln-Washington, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0632)
  - Photo Unit #: B055 Ralph Thorton, filing clerk in Commissariat, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0633)
  - Photo Unit #: B056 Major Robert Merriman, Chief of Brigade Staff, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0634)
  - Photo Unit #: B057 Major Robert Merriman, Chief of Brigade Staff, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0635)
  - Photo Unit #: B058 Major Robert Merriman, Chief of Brigade staff, 1937-12 (Box 5, Folder 11-1278)
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/12)
  - Photo Unit #: B059 Captain Rollin Dart, Brigade Staff, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0636)
  - Photo Unit #: B060 Captain Rollin Dart, Brigade Staff, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0637)
  - Photo Unit #: B061 John Hunter, Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company 1, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0638)
  - Photo Unit #: B063 John Hunter, Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company 1, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0639)
  - Photo Unit #: B065 Captain Robert Thompson, Battalion Commander, MacKenzie-Papineau, 1937-12 (Box 1, Folder 11-0117)
  - Photo Unit #: B066 Captain Robert Thompson, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1841)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/36)
  - Photo Unit #: B067 Louis Secundy, Chief of Auto Park, 1937-12 (Box 5, Folder 11-1279)
  - Photo Unit #: B068 Louis Secundy, Chief of Auto Park, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0640)
  - Photo Unit #: B069 Joseph Dion, Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0641)
  - Photo Unit #: B070 [?] Anderson, Danish Seaman, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0642)
  - Photo Unit #: B071 Hans Kaltschmidt, Adjuntant to Chief of Brigade, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0643)
  - Photo Unit #: B072 Nathan Weisenfeld, Chief of Brigade Runners, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0898)
  - Photo Unit #: B073 Elhanon Winchester Bridges, Company 3, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0899)
  - Photo Unit #: B074 Milton Gale, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Political Commissar, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0900)
  - Photo Unit #: B076 James Bourne, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0644)
  - Photo Unit #: B077 John Robinson, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0645)
  - Photo Unit #: B078 Paul White, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0646)
  - Photo Unit #: B080 Sid Rosenthall [?], Lincoln-Washington Battalion Clerk, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0647)
  - Photo Unit #: B082 Vincent Sanchis, Adjuntant of Company 3, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0901)
  - Photo Unit #: B083 Samuel Willis, MacKenzie-Papineau Scout, 1937-11 (Box 5, Folder 11-1280)
  - Photo Unit #: B084 Nulo Makela, undated (Box 5, Folder 11-1281)
  - Photo Unit #: B086 Thoman Mallon, Political Commissar, Machine-Gunner Company, MacKenzie-Papineau, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0902)
  - Photo Unit #: B087 Eugene Nolte, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Secretary, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0903)
  - Photo Unit #: B088 James Craddock, MacKenzie-Papineau Chief of Staff, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0648)
  - Photo Unit #: B089 Claude Pringle, MacKenzie-Papineau souper, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0904)
  - Photo Unit #: B090 Thomas Norton from Reed College, Portland, Oregon, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0649)
  - Photo Unit #: B095 James Cox, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0650)
  - Photo Unit #: B096 Irving Halpern, Brigade motorcyclist, 1937-11 (Box 5, Folder 11-1282)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Print
  - Photo Unit #: B097 Major [?] Crespo, Brigade Staff, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0651)
  - Photo Unit #: B098 Lieutenant Harry Poll [Pollitt?], 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0652)
  - Photo Unit #: B099 Albert Chisholm, artist for Brigade Bulletin, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0653)
  - Photo Unit #: B100 Larry Dukes, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0654)
  - Photo Unit #: B101 Edward Bender, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0655)
  - Photo Unit #: B102 George Kaye, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0656)
  - Photo Unit #: B103 Robert Thompson, Captain, MacKenzie-Papineau, 1937-11 (Box 5, Folder 11-1283)
  - Photo Unit #: B104 Pat Barcena [Isador (Frank) Barcena?], Transmiciones [Transmissions], 1937-11 (Box 1, Folder 11-0001)
  - Photo Unit #: B106 Jacob Kramer, Transmiciones [Transmissions] driver, 1937-11 (Box 1, Folder 11-0002)
  - Photo Unit #: B110 Ernest Kozlowski, brigade scout, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0905)
  - Photo Unit #: B111 Arthur Landis, MacKenzie-Papineau topographer, 1937-11 (Box 1, Folder 11-0003)
  - Photo Unit #: B114 David Gordon of Brigade Commissariat, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0906)
  - Photo Unit #: B115 David Gordon of Brigade Commissariat, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0907)
  - Photo Unit #: B116 Emiliano Marin, Cuban in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0657)
  - Photo Unit #: B117 Thain Summers, officers training school, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0658)
  - Photo Unit #: B118 Joseph Taylor, Brigade scout, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0659)
  - Photo Unit #: B119 Albert Chisholm, artist on commissariat staff, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0660)
  - Photo Unit #: B120 Captain Philip Detro, Chief, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-11 (Box 5, Folder 11-1284)
  - Photo Unit #: B121 [?] Rosenstein, one of the original Lincoln Boys, 1937-11 (Box 2, Folder 11-0661)
  - Photo Unit #: B122 Benjamin Katine, 15th International Brigade photographer, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0908)
  - Photo Unit #: B123 Benjamin Katine, 15th International Brigade photographer, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0909)
  - Photo Unit #: B124 Jack Mullinger, Chief of Scouts, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0910)
    (Moscow Number: 5/188/89)
  - Photo Unit #: B126 Michael Pavlos, chief cook in Estado Mayor [Headquarters] kitchen, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0911)
  - Photo Unit #: B127 William Oderaka, Lab. Assistant in Photo Department, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0912)
  - Photo Unit #: B128 William Buchkowski, Political Commissar of Brigade Scouts, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0913)
  - Photo Unit #: B132 Charles Kersh, driver in Auto Park, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0914)
  - Photo Unit #: B133 [?] Gallinat of Transmiciones [Transmissions], 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0915)
  - Photo Unit #: B134 Max Farrar, cook in Estado Mayor [Headquarters] kitchen, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0916)
  - Photo Unit #: B135 Albert Harris, 15th International Brigade Intendencia, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0917)
  - Photo Unit #: B136 William Frame, Intendencia, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0662)
  - Photo Unit #: B137 Fredrick Lutz, Political Commissar, Intendencia, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0663)
  - Photo Unit #: B138 Thomas O'Malley, Intendencia, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0664)
  - Photo Unit #: B140 Dr. Luis Diaz Soto, Lincoln-Washington medical staff, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0665)
  - Photo Unit #: B141 Dr. Luis Diaz Soto, Lincoln-Washington medical staff, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0666)
  - Photo Unit #: B143 Arthur Landis of MacKenzie-Papineau at Brigade Mapping School, 1937-12 (Box 1, Folder 11-0004)
  - Photo Unit #: B144 Dionesio Aleman (Cuban), Chief, Company 2, 24th Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0918)
  - Photo Unit #: B145 Angel Garcia of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0919)
  - Photo Unit #: B146 Harry Schoenberg, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 5, Folder 11-1285)
  - Photo Unit #: B147 Edward Cecil Smith, Captain of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 5, Folder 11-1286)
  - Photo Unit #: B148 Joseph Kaplan, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0920)
  - Photo Unit #: B151 José María Varela, 15th International Brigade Commissar, 1937-12 (Box 5, Folder 11-1287)
  - Photo Unit #: B157 Enrique Santana Torregroso, Sergeant, 24th Battalion, distinguished, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0921)
  - Photo Unit #: B169 John Givulinovich, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0922)
  - Photo Unit #: B170 Frank Migone Flores, Political Commissariat Member, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0923)
  - Photo Unit #: B171 Bert Jackson, mapper for Brigade, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0667)
  - Photo Unit #: B173 Manuel [?] Dong Hong Yick, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0924)
  - Photo Unit #: B175 John William Snyder [?], Cabo, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0925)
  - Photo Unit #: B176 Horace Kark, Cabo, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0926)
  - Photo Unit #: B177 Lawrence Kleidman, Cabo, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 5, Folder 11-1290)
  - Photo Unit #: B178 Charles Kuchs [?], driver, Auto Park, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0927)
  - Photo Unit #: B179 [Benjamin] Butch Goldstein, Cabo, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 5, Folder 11-1291)
  - Photo Unit #: B180 John Washington, Cabo, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0928)
  - Photo Unit #: B184 Wally Tapsell, undated (Box 5, Folder 11-1292)
  - Photo Unit #: B188 John [?] Hunter (or Oscar Hunter), 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0929)
  - Photo Unit #: B190 Sergeant Elliot Loomis (Transmiciones [Transmissions]), 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0930)
  - Photo Unit #: B193 Sidney Bassin, 15th Brigade Auto Park Chauffeur, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0931)
  - Photo Unit #: B196 Sergeant Harry W. Randall, Jr. Brigade Photographer, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0932)
  - Photo Unit #: B197 Milford Chapin (Blackie, "Idaho"), MacKenzie-Papineau cook, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0933)
  - Photo Unit #: B198 Walter "Kid" O'Kane, (Transmiciones [Transmissions]), 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0934)
  - Photo Unit #: B199 Wilfred Cowan, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0935)
  - Photo Unit #: B200 John Givulinovich [alias John Givins], MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Intendencia, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0936)
  - Photo Unit #: B201 Salman Salzman (Palestine), MacKenzie-Papineau, Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0937)
  - Photo Unit #: B202 Captain Alfredo Balsa, 1937-12 (Box 5, Folder 11-1293)
  - Photo Unit #: B203 Paddy Stafford, British anti-tank battery, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0938)
  - Photo Unit #: B204 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Commander, 15th International Brigade, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0939)
  - Photo Unit #: B208 Fred Keller, Political Commissar, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0940)
  - Photo Unit #: B209 Ben Kasinap, first aid man in Transmiciones [Transmissions], 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0668)
  - Photo Unit #: B212 Argente, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0941)